# Written by JennJenn
# Original file from: https://github.com/Cog-Creators/Red-DiscordBot/blob/V3/develop/redbot/cogs/trivia/data/lists/leagueults.yaml
questions:
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Absolute Zero?"
  answers:
  - Nunu
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Abyssal Voyage?"
  answers:
  - Tahm Kench
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Ace in the Hole?"
  answers:
  - Caitlyn
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Aspect of the Cougar?"
  answers:
  - Nidalee
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Assault and Battery?"
  answers:
  - Vi
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Behind Enemy Lines?"
  answers:
  - Quinn
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Blade of the Exile?"
  answers:
  - Riven
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Bullet Time?"
  answers:
  - Miss Fortune
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Buster Shot?"
  answers:
  - Tristana
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Call of the Forge God?"
  answers:
  - Ornn
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Cannon Barrage?"
  answers:
  - Gangplank
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Cataclysm?"
  answers:
  - Jarvan
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Chaaaaaaaarge!!! ?"
  answers:
  - Kled
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Chain of Corruption?"
  answers:
  - Varus
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Chaos Storm?"
  answers:
  - Viktor
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Children of the Grave?"
  answers:
  - Mordekaiser
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Chronobreak?"
  answers:
  - Ekko
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Chronoshift?"
  answers:
  - Zilean
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Chum the Waters?"
  answers:
  - Fizz
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Collateral Damage?"
  answers:
  - Graves
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Command: Shockwave?"
  answers:
  - Orianna
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Cosmic Radiance?"
  answers:
  - Taric
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Crescendo?"
  answers:
  - Sona
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Crescent Sweep?"
  answers:
  - Xin Zhao
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Crowstorm?"
  answers:
  - Fiddlesticks
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Curse of the Sad Mummy?"
  answers:
  - Amumu
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Curtain Call?"
  answers:
  - Jhin
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Cyclone?"
  answers:
  - Wukong
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Daisy!?"
  answers:
  - Ivern
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Death Lotus?"
  answers:
  - Katarina
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Death Mark?"
  answers:
  - Zed
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Demacian Justice?"
  answers:
  - Garen
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Demonic Ascension?"
  answers:
  - Swain
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Depth Charge?"
  answers:
  - Nautilus
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Destiny?"
  answers:
  - Twisted Fate
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Dominus?"
  answers:
  - Renekton
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Dragon's Descent?"
  answers:
  - Shyvana
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Dragon's Rage?"
  answers:
  - Lee Sin
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Emperor's Divide?"
  answers:
  - Azir
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Enchanted Crystal Arrow?"
  answers:
  - Ashe
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Eulogy of the Isles?"
  answers:
  - Yorick
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Explosive Cask?"
  answers:
  - Gragas
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Fate's Call?"
  answers:
  - Kalista
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Fear Beyond Death?"
  answers:
  - Urgot
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Feast?"
  answers:
  - Cho'Gath
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Featherstorm?"
  answers:
  - Xayah
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Final Hour?"
  answers:
  - Vayne
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Final Spark?"
  answers:
  - Lux
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Frozen Tomb?"
  answers:
  - Lissandra
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Fury of the Sands?"
  answers:
  - Nasus
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: GNAR!"
  answers:
  - Gnar
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Glacial Fissure?"
  answers:
  - Braum
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Glacial Prison?"
  answers:
  - Sejuani
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Glacial Storm?"
  answers:
  - Anivia
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Grand Challenge?"
  answers:
  - Fiora
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Grand Skyfall?"
  answers:
  - Pantheon
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Grandmaster's Might?"
  answers:
  - Jax
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Hallucinate?"
  answers:
  - Shaco
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Hemoplague?"
  answers:
  - Vladimir
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Hero's Entrance?"
  answers:
  - Galio
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Hextech Ultimatum?"
  answers:
  - Camille
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Highlander?"
  answers:
  - Master Yi
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Impale?"
  answers:
  - Skarner
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Infinite Duress?"
  answers:
  - Warwick
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Insanity Potion?"
  answers:
  - Singed
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Intervention?"
  answers:
  - Kayle
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Keeper's Verdict?"
  answers:
  - Poppy
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Killer Instinct?"
  answers:
  - Kai'Sa
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Lamb's Respite?"
  answers:
  - Kindred
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Last Breath?"
  answers:
  - Yasuo
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Last Caress?"
  answers:
  - Evelynn
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Leap of Faith?"
  answers:
  - Illaoi
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Let's Bounce!"
  answers:
  - Zac
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Life Form Disintegration Ray?"
  answers:
  - Vel'Koz
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Living Artillery?"
  answers:
  - Kog'Maw
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Lunar Rush?"
  answers:
  - Diana
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Mantra?"
  answers:
  - Karma
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Massacre?"
  answers:
  - Aatrox
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Mega Inferno Bomb?"
  answers:
  - Ziggs
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Mercury Cannon/Mercury Hammer?"
  answers:
  - Jayce
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Mimic?"
  answers:
  - Leblanc
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Missile Barrage?"
  answers:
  - Corki
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Monsoon?"
  answers:
  - Janna
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Nether Grasp?"
  answers:
  - Malzahar
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Noxian Guillotine?"
  answers:
  - Darius
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Noxious Trap?"
  answers:
  - Teemo
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: On The Hunt?"
  answers:
  - Sivir
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Onslaught of Shadows?"
  answers:
  - Hecarim
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Paranoia?"
  answers:
  - Nocturne
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Petrifying Gaze?"
  answers:
  - Cassiopeia
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Pheonix Stance?"
  answers:
  - Udyr
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Portal Jump?"
  answers:
  - Zoe
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Primordial Burst?"
  answers:
  - Veigar
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Pyroclasm?"
  answers:
  - Brand
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Ragnarok?"
  answers:
  - Olaf
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Rat-Ta-Tat-Tat?"
  answers:
  - Twitch
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Realm Warp?"
  answers:
  - Ryze
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Requiem?"
  answers:
  - Karthus
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Riftwalk?"
  answers:
  - Kassadin
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Rite of the Arcane?"
  answers:
  - Xerath
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Sadism?"
  answers:
  - Dr. Mundo
  - Mundo
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Shadow Assault?"
  answers:
  - Talon
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Shadow Dance?"
  answers:
  - Akali
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Slicing Maelstrom?"
  answers:
  - Kennen
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Solar Flare?"
  answers:
  - Leona
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Soul Shackles?"
  answers:
  - Morgana
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Spider Form/Human Form?"
  answers:
  - Elise
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Spirit Rush?"
  answers:
  - Ahri
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Stand United?"
  answers:
  - Shen
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Static Field?"
  answers:
  - Blitzcrank
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Stranglethorns?"
  answers:
  - Zyra
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Subjugate?"
  answers:
  - Trundle
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Summon: Tibbers?"
  answers:
  - Annie
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Super Mega Death Rocket!"
  answers:
  - Jinx
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Tempered Fate?"
  answers:
  - Bard
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: The Box?"
  answers:
  - Thresh
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: The Culling?"
  answers:
  - Lucian
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: The Equalizer?"
  answers:
  - Rumble
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: The Quickness?"
  answers:
  - Rakan
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Thrill of the Hunt?"
  answers:
  - Rengar
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Thunder Claws?"
  answers:
  - Volibear
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Tidal Wave?"
  answers:
  - Nami
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Tremors?"
  answers:
  - Rammus
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Trueshot Barrage?"
  answers:
  - Ezreal
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: UPGRADE!!! ?"
  answers:
  - Heimerdinger
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Umbral Trespass?"
  answers:
  - Kayn
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Unbreakable Will?"
  answers:
  - Alistar
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Undying Rage?"
  answers:
  - Tryndamere
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Unleashed Power?"
  answers:
  - Syndra
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Unstoppable Force?"
  answers:
  - Malphite
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Unstoppable Onslaught?"
  answers:
  - Sion
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Vanguard's Edge?"
  answers:
  - Irelia
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Vengeful Maelstrom?"
  answers:
  - Maokai
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Voice of Light?"
  answers:
  - Aurelion Sol
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Void Assault?"
  answers:
  - Kha'Zix
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Void Rush?"
  answers:
  - Rek'Sai
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Weaver's Wall?"
  answers:
  - Taliyah
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Whirling Death?"
  answers:
  - Draven
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Wild Growth?"
  answers:
  - Lulu
- question: "Which champion's ultimate is named: Wish?"
  answers:
  - Soraka